<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-13T21:10:40+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Phlow Magazine</title><subtitle>Phlow-Magazine.com is a magazine about free mp3 music released under a creative commons. You can legally download all the mp3s on this website.</subtitle><author><name>Moritz »mo.« Sauer</name></author><entry><title type="html">Ras Amerlock – »A Bass Oddity – Trinity All Star« (LibreCommeLair)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/dub-reggae/1667-ras-amerlock-a-bass-oddity" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ras Amerlock – »A Bass Oddity – Trinity All Star« (LibreCommeLair)" /><published>2017-02-15T13:21:08+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-15T13:21:08+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/dub-reggae/ras-amerlock-a-bass-oddity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/dub-reggae/1667-ras-amerlock-a-bass-oddity">**** I love unique websites, unique sounds and of course high quality. The french dub netlabel LCL aka LibreCommeLair has everything. A website with a unique hand-made look, a dedication to reggae in all kinds of tastes and a bunch of musicians releasing wonderful productions. The »Juggernaut of an EP« is a classy slice of music by Ras Amerlock on the french dub netlabel.
&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;!--mp3links--&gt;

[Ras Amerlock - &quot;7th Sea Dub in Twilight&quot; (MP3)](http://www.lclweb.org/audio/releases/lcl20_abo/%5BLCL20%5D_Ras_Amerlock_-_2010_A_Bass_Oddity_-_02_-_7th_Sea_Dub_in_twilight_-_Ras_Amerlock_meets_Professor_Balthazar.mp3)
  
[Ras Amerlock - &quot;Santiago meets Pacho'Merlock&quot; (MP3)](http://www.lclweb.org/audio/releases/lcl20_abo/%5BLCL20%5D_Ras_Amerlock_-_2010_A_Bass_Oddity_-_03_-_Santiago_Meets_Pacho_Merlock.mp3)
  
[Ras Amerlock - &quot;Pre Historiker Dub&quot; (MP3)](http://www.lclweb.org/audio/releases/lcl20_abo/%5BLCL20%5D_Ras_Amerlock_-_2010_A_Bass_Oddity_-_01_-_Pre_Historiker_Dub_-_Ras_Amerlock_meets_Uffe.mp3)

&lt;!--mp3linksend--&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;!--adsense--&gt;

One of those allready well-known artists in the world of creative commons reggae is Ras Amerlock. The American already released several times on [Jahtari]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/?s=Jahtari). So it's no surprise, that the close relationship between LCL and Jahtari convinced him to release his groovy bass odditiy on LCL.

## MP3 Reggae Music Download

**Download:** Ras Amerlock - &quot;A Bass Oddity (Trinity All Star)&quot; (ZIP-Archive)
  
**Artist-Website:** [Ras Amerlock](http://www.myspace.com/rasamerlockstatemonrasta)
  
**Release:** [Ras Amerlock - &quot;A Bass Oddity (Trinity All Star)&quot;](http://www.lclweb.org/audio_lp_lcl20.htm)
  
**Netlabel:** [LibreCommeLair aka LCL](http://www.lclweb.org)</content><author><name>Moritz »mo.« Sauer</name></author><category term="lcl" /><category term="LibreCommeLair" /><category term="Ras Amerlock" /><summary type="html">** I love unique websites, unique sounds and of course high quality. The french dub netlabel LCL aka LibreCommeLair has everything. A website with a unique hand-made look, a dedication to reggae in all kinds of tastes and a bunch of musicians releasing wonderful productions. The »Juggernaut of an EP« is a classy slice of music by Ras Amerlock on the french dub netlabel.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/cover_ras_amerlock_bass_odditiy.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Best Of Netlabels: »Their Finest Hour Vol. 3«</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/free-compilation/411-netlabel-compilation-their-finest-hour-3" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best Of Netlabels: »Their Finest Hour Vol. 3«" /><published>2011-01-10T02:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2011-01-10T02:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/free-compilation/netlabel-compilation-their-finest-hour-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/free-compilation/411-netlabel-compilation-their-finest-hour-3">We don't care about genres! Of course, we cultivate our preferences like everyone. But we try to stay open-minded as possible as we can. Convinced that **the only way to discover new worlds is to share**, to communicate and to listen to each other, we proudly present you the [third edition of our Phlow-Netlabel-Serie]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/free-compilation/411-netlabel-compilation-their-finest-hour-3). We dived into the deep ocean of free music and came back with this adventurous compilation. Explore with us music from all over the globe, from Indie-Pop to Techno to Drum'n'Bass to Ambient.&lt;!--more--&gt;

## mo.'s little note

[Soto]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/pop/265-soto-soto-ep-creation-centre) was the brightest discovery for me in March. While fumbling around with my telescope to discover new electronic music, Sven published his wonderful discovery. The pop-group from Japan sneaked directly into my heart and that's why Soto had to be the hugging brace for our third Best-Of-Netlabels-compilation.

As always we tried hard to combine the most impressive music-moments to one phlowtin' music-sampler. I hope you enjoy the diversity of sounds... And if you do so: **Smile back and leave a note on the websites of your favorite musicians!** They're thirsty for feedback, so why not saying: Thank you for your music!

Greets from Cologne/Germany, Yours mo.

## Playlist &quot;Their Finest Hour Vol. 3&quot;

  1. [&quot;My Blue Plane (soto version)&quot; from Soto]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/pop/265-soto-soto-ep-creation-centre)
  2. [&quot;Did The Red Sea Part?&quot; from Ghost Bees]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/hiphop/396-various-52-weeks-winter-peppermill-records)
  3. [&quot;I'm on your side&quot; from Henrik José]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/electronica-indietronic/241-va-cycles-camomille-netlabel)
  4. [&quot;The Giant Squid from My Awesome Mixtape]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/electronica-indietronic/368-my-awesome-mixtape-songs-of-sadness-songs-of-happiness-kirstens-postcard)
  5. [&quot;agrippa's trilemma&quot; from gillicuddy]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/pop/335-gillicuddy-shmalhans-is-kuechenmeister)
  6. [&quot;Pension Tension&quot; from Cactus On Fire feat. Baba Brinkman]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/hiphop/396-various-52-weeks-winter-peppermill-records)
  7. [&quot;Walk home&quot; from Velure]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/trip-hop/350-velure-songbox-ideology)
  8. [&quot;rhode-o&quot; from sabian]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/drum-and-bass/398-va-kapitel-1-konsum-productions)
  9. [&quot;Dorian Concept&quot; from Mickey Eats Plastic]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/wp-admin/post.php?action=edit&amp;post=258)
 10. [&quot;Da Try Bute&quot; from Apes on Tapes]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/hiphop/283-apes-on-tapes-you-open-homework-records)
 11. [&quot;Take Me Beyond (Paul Keeley Remix)&quot; from Vincent Casanova]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/interview-portrait/370-tribute-to-epsilonlab-netlabel)
 12. [&quot;Rise And Fall&quot; from Evolent]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/techno/362-evolent-rise-and-fall-plex-netlabel)
 13. [&quot;mr. illusion&quot; from dataman]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/feature/359-run-for-cover-2-the-flash-cover-art-from-n-netlabel)
 14. [&quot;ammettiamo...&quot; from Seralf]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/interview-portrait/325-dharmasound-netlabel-interview)
 15. [&quot;Orange&quot; from Soto]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/mp3-music-download/pop/265-soto-soto-ep-creation-centre)

## Free MP3 Music Download

Listen &amp; Stream: [Start Playlist now!](http://www.archive.org/download/their_finest_hour_vol3/their_finest_hour_vol_3_playlist.m3u)
  
  
Cover: [Download our Cover Artwork - Their Finest Hour Vol 3]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/images/cover-their-finest-hour-3-720x720.jpg &quot;Cover Artwork - Their Finest Hour Vol 3&quot;)

## Information about the Cover-Artwork

The artwork was composed by mo. But the main respect goes to the photographer Taro Taylor who shot [this amazing photo](http://flickr.com/photos/tjt195/2330012633/). You find [Taro's portfolio on flickr.com](http://flickr.com/photos/tjt195/). Fortunately he released his colourful shot under [a creative commons](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.0/deed.de).</content><author><name>Moritz »mo.« Sauer</name></author><category term="compilation" /><category term="download" /><category term="free" /><category term="mp3" /><category term="music" /><category term="netlabel" /><category term="phlow compilation" /><summary type="html">We don’t care about genres! Of course, we cultivate our preferences like everyone. But we try to stay open-minded as possible as we can. Convinced that the only way to discover new worlds is to share, to communicate and to listen to each other, we proudly present you the third edition of our Phlow-Netlabel-Serie. We dived into the deep ocean of free music and came back with this adventurous compilation. Explore with us music from all over the globe, from Indie-Pop to Techno to Drum’n’Bass to Ambient.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/cover-their-finest-hour-3-500x500.jpg%22,%20%22caption%22=%3E%22Photo:%20%3Ca%20href=%5C%22http://flickr.com/photos/tjt195/%5C%22%3ETaro%20Taylor%3C/a%3E%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Tracky Birthday – »Animal Audition« (upitup Netlabel)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/1088-tracky-birthday-animal-audition-upitup-netlabel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tracky Birthday – »Animal Audition« (upitup Netlabel)" /><published>2011-01-01T15:08:29+01:00</published><updated>2011-01-01T15:08:29+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/tracky-birthday-animal-audition-upitup-netlabel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/1088-tracky-birthday-animal-audition-upitup-netlabel">Tracky Birthday is one of those artists, who push out his majestry of artistry through every pore of his body. While reflecting society and its desire to show off in his Video-Series &quot;Bootyclipse&quot;, his website makes fun of all that Web 2.0-Dingeling. And till then, you haven't heard his mind-twisting raps full of satirical rhymes. &quot;Animal Audition&quot; haunts you with its Funk, Samples and absorbing grooves.
&lt;!--more--&gt;

{% include mp3 %}

Infrequently I stumble upon musicians who really impress me. Most of the time musicians only think about their music, compose good or bad songs and often forget about entertainment and other arts. On the contrary Tracky Birthday introduces you to music by letting you see the full scope.

His raps won't introduce you to the world of BlingBling-Diamond-Shit. Neither they'll throw some trash on you of his ghetto-childhood. No, in his raps and music Tracky Birthday reflects our society in the digital age. It's an album filled with music history. An album which mashes up sound of our computer-childhood with pop-anthems from Michael Jackson.

![tracky-birthday-feature]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/images/tracky-birthday-feature.jpg &quot;tracky-birthday-feature&quot;)

And on top you listen to fast raps, playing with the english language like a true digital native. Rub your ears for this incredible german rapper, born into a global world where we all live in.

Meet Tracky Birthday where the Wu meets the Bat...

## Bootyclipse

Tracky Birthday aka Dennis Knopf won a Prize for Online Art at the 22nd Filmwinter Festival 2009 for his [Bootyclipse Video Series](http://www.youtube.com/dennisknopf). Watch this video and enjoy!

&gt; In the summer of 2007, a German rapper and a debutant net artist Dennis Knopf opened a channel on YouTube that he named Bootyclipse. Every video broadcasted on that channel consists of those candid moments, prolonged to 40-60 seconds. Dennis has collected fragments from more than twenty videos where a girl who is going to shake her booty in front of a camera has not appeared in the frame yet, and looped these moments, leaving the music to play in real time. [Read more in on this website...](http://art.teleportacia.org/observation/infinite_seance_2/) (scroll down on the page to read the excerpt)[](http://art.teleportacia.org/observation/infinite_seance_2/)</content><author><name>Brigitte</name></author><category term="download" /><category term="free" /><category term="Hip Hop" /><category term="mp3" /><category term="music" /><category term="netlabel" /><summary type="html">Tracky Birthday is one of those artists, who push out his majestry of artistry through every pore of his body. While reflecting society and its desire to show off in his Video-Series “Bootyclipse”, his website makes fun of all that Web 2.0-Dingeling. And till then, you haven’t heard his mind-twisting raps full of satirical rhymes. “Animal Audition” haunts you with its Funk, Samples and absorbing grooves.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/animal_audition.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Superloader – »Fusion« (Supafeed Netlabel)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/house/1442-superloader-fusion-supafeed-netlabel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Superloader – »Fusion« (Supafeed Netlabel)" /><published>2011-01-01T04:01:46+01:00</published><updated>2011-01-01T04:01:46+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/house/superloader-fusion-supafeed-netlabel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/house/1442-superloader-fusion-supafeed-netlabel">If you like Deep House Music with a juicy kickdrum and a relaxed mood, Supafeed is the netlabel of choice. Nearly every release sweets up the dancefloor. Superloader makes no exception and the power of his tunes - like his fellow mates on Supafeed - come from the stoic grooves, some little chords and the continous trippin on a mellow vibe.

- Superloader - &quot;Let if off!&quot; (MP3)
- Superloader - &quot;Fusion&quot; (MP3)
- Superloader - &quot;Wig Wam Bam&quot; (MP3)

Superloader makes that sort of house music which seems to never stop. If you're not down in the club with the crew, you feel the lax mood. The night is long and Supafeed sucks us into that endless groove we get hypnotized by the whole night. Just take &quot;Let it off&quot;. You start the track and the groove is there. It will still be the same, when the track stops. Nevertheless you get some damn nice sounds while seesawing under the disco ball with Superloader.

_**Grab the love handles of your girlfriend and drag her onto the dancefloor!**_</content><author><name>Moritz »mo.« Sauer</name></author><category term="Deephouse" /><category term="House" /><category term="supafeed" /><category term="Superloader" /><summary type="html">If you like Deep House Music with a juicy kickdrum and a relaxed mood, Supafeed is the netlabel of choice. Nearly every release sweets up the dancefloor. Superloader makes no exception and the power of his tunes - like his fellow mates on Supafeed - come from the stoic grooves, some little chords and the continous trippin on a mellow vibe. Superloader - “Let if off!” (MP3) Superloader - “Fusion” (MP3) Superloader - “Wig Wam Bam” (MP3) Superloader makes that sort of house music which seems to never stop. If you’re not down in the club with the crew, you feel the lax mood. The night is long and Supafeed sucks us into that endless groove we get hypnotized by the whole night. Just take “Let it off”. You start the track and the groove is there. It will still be the same, when the track stops. Nevertheless you get some damn nice sounds while seesawing under the disco ball with Superloader. Grab the love handles of your girlfriend and drag her onto the dancefloor!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/superloader_cover008.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Bitbasic – »Sprinkling Rainbows« (Monotonik Netlabel)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/drum-and-bass/1359-bitbasic-sprinkling-rainbows-monotonik-netlabel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bitbasic – »Sprinkling Rainbows« (Monotonik Netlabel)" /><published>2010-12-29T14:47:07+01:00</published><updated>2010-12-29T14:47:07+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/drum-and-bass/bitbasic-sprinkling-rainbows-monotonik-netlabel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/drum-and-bass/1359-bitbasic-sprinkling-rainbows-monotonik-netlabel">Bitbasic's new album Sprinkling Rainbows, released on Monotonik, delves deep into the world of smooth and funky Jazz stylings, in a follow up the 2007 &quot;Grating Rainbows EP&quot;. This is an album of deft and clever combinations that soothe and then surprise the listener, as exquisite jazz chords and chromatics give way to drill and bass rasps and glitchy repetition, before falling luxuriously back into a pleasing bath of strings or mellow guitar. Bitbasic presents music that plays on the tensions between heavily quantized, truncated sound and free style playing; indulging in a playground of cut ups and programming.

{% include mp3 %}

At over fifty minutes, this wonderfully cohesive album treats the listener to a variety of gear shifts and mood changes that make the whole experience engaging and enervating from beginning to end. Whether it is the rapid, funky breaks and signature changes of &quot;Realization&quot;, the acoustic guitar sound, descending Resident style analogue synth sighs and stuttering, reverby drums of &quot;Damaged Beyond Repair&quot;, or the surprising but beautifully executed cover of &quot;Ain't No Sunshine&quot;, this is an album that will make you grin at the pleasure of it all.

At some point during Roxy and Elsewhere, Frank Zappa declares that &quot;Jazz isn’t dead, it just smells funny&quot;: a statement that adroitly encapsulated the moribund state of much of what jazz had become by the mid 1970’s. For Zappa, a playful and creative engagement with jazz, and his combinations thereof with other musical styles, served as a platform for countless reinventions. While George Duke, Ruth Underwood, Don Preston, Napolean Murphy Brock et al may have been superseded by samples, perhaps, in some tenuous way, Bitbasic’s Sprinkling Rainbows is another step along a path of enlightened, intelligent and wry experimentation.

**Review written by Greg Healey.**</content><author><name>Greg</name></author><category term="bitbasic" /><category term="drill and bass" /><category term="drum'n'bass" /><category term="Jazz" /><category term="monotonik" /><category term="netlabel" /><summary type="html">Bitbasic’s new album Sprinkling Rainbows, released on Monotonik, delves deep into the world of smooth and funky Jazz stylings, in a follow up the 2007 “Grating Rainbows EP”. This is an album of deft and clever combinations that soothe and then surprise the listener, as exquisite jazz chords and chromatics give way to drill and bass rasps and glitchy repetition, before falling luxuriously back into a pleasing bath of strings or mellow guitar. Bitbasic presents music that plays on the tensions between heavily quantized, truncated sound and free style playing; indulging in a playground of cut ups and programming. MP3 – Click to listen Realization Damaged Beyond Repair Aint No Sunshine At over fifty minutes, this wonderfully cohesive album treats the listener to a variety of gear shifts and mood changes that make the whole experience engaging and enervating from beginning to end. Whether it is the rapid, funky breaks and signature changes of “Realization”, the acoustic guitar sound, descending Resident style analogue synth sighs and stuttering, reverby drums of “Damaged Beyond Repair”, or the surprising but beautifully executed cover of “Ain’t No Sunshine”, this is an album that will make you grin at the pleasure of it all. At some point during Roxy and Elsewhere, Frank Zappa declares that “Jazz isn’t dead, it just smells funny”: a statement that adroitly encapsulated the moribund state of much of what jazz had become by the mid 1970’s. For Zappa, a playful and creative engagement with jazz, and his combinations thereof with other musical styles, served as a platform for countless reinventions. While George Duke, Ruth Underwood, Don Preston, Napolean Murphy Brock et al may have been superseded by samples, perhaps, in some tenuous way, Bitbasic’s Sprinkling Rainbows is another step along a path of enlightened, intelligent and wry experimentation. Review written by Greg Healey.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/bitbasic-mtk213.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">AEED – »Synesthesia« (Error Broadcast Netlabel)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/1282-aeed-synesthesia-error-broadcast-netlabel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEED – »Synesthesia« (Error Broadcast Netlabel)" /><published>2010-12-29T06:47:16+01:00</published><updated>2010-12-29T06:47:16+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/aeed-synesthesia-error-broadcast-netlabel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/1282-aeed-synesthesia-error-broadcast-netlabel">***Fine Instrumental Hip Hop*** // Instrumental Hip Hop kicks me currently the most. I waited a long time for more releases like &quot;Synesthesia&quot; that stand in the tradition of music by [Comfort Fit]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/tag/comfort-fit) or my beloved Flying Lotus. AEED pushes Hip Hop music into the right direction. Playful rhythmic arrangements, definetely electronic and with a funky flavor. Music that makes us grin and nod happily.

[AEED &quot;Cry Now&quot;](http://www.error-broadcast.com/releases/ebc002/ebc002_aeed_03_cry_now.mp3.mp3)
  
[AEED &quot;Elektricity&quot;](http://www.error-broadcast.com/releases/ebc002/ebc002_aeed_02_elektricity.mp3.mp3)

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;!--adsense--&gt;

&quot;Synesthesia&quot; is colourful like the album cover itself. Listen to that pop appeal in &quot;Cry now&quot;. AEED rolls out the bass as a pumping fundament and than gets lost in melodies. This album has nothing to do with loop-orientated Hip Hop instrumentals. AEED feds his music with sweeping synths, funky or jazzy melodies which seem to glide easily from the keyboard into the corners of his broken beats.

Sometimes &quot;Synesthesia&quot; is full of melancholy like in &quot;Strange Dreams&quot;. Sometimes AEED delivers us funky anthems like &quot;Elephants Dance&quot; bouncing on a sparkeling bassline. If you like electronica, chip music and if you have some b-boy-blood in your venes. This is the exact soundtrack. Error Broadcast gets bigger with each new release. Can't wait for more eye candy!

## MP3 Hip Hop Music Download

**Download:** [AEED - &quot;Synesthesia&quot; (ZIP-Archive)](http://grandmasterrobo.sonicsquirrel.net/Error_Broadcast/EBC002/ebc002_aeed_synesthesia.zip)
  
**Artist-Website:** [www.myspace.com/aeedmusic](http://www.myspace.com/aeedmusic)
  
**Release:** [AEED - &quot;Synesthesia&quot;](http://www.error-broadcast.com/index.php/releases/show/release/ebc002)
  
**Netlabel:** [www.error-broadcast.com](http://www.error-broadcast.com)</content><author><name>Brigitte</name></author><category term="aeed" /><category term="download" /><category term="error broadcast" /><category term="free" /><category term="Hip Hop" /><category term="Instrumental" /><category term="mp3" /><category term="music" /><category term="netlabel" /><summary type="html">Fine Instrumental Hip Hop // Instrumental Hip Hop kicks me currently the most. I waited a long time for more releases like “Synesthesia” that stand in the tradition of music by Comfort Fit or my beloved Flying Lotus. AEED pushes Hip Hop music into the right direction. Playful rhythmic arrangements, definetely electronic and with a funky flavor. Music that makes us grin and nod happily. AEED “Cry Now” AEED “Elektricity”</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/ebc002_aeed_synesthesia_cover.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Various – »A New Chapter Of Acid House!« (Tribe Toolz)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/house/1655-a-new-chapter-of-acid-house" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Various – »A New Chapter Of Acid House!« (Tribe Toolz)" /><published>2010-12-27T21:12:32+01:00</published><updated>2010-12-27T21:12:32+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/house/a-new-chapter-of-acid-house</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/house/1655-a-new-chapter-of-acid-house">***Aciiiiid!*** // If we believe the peepz at Tribe Toolz today is the (un)official birthday of the fabulous Roland TB-303 synthesizer. No synthesizer - except the drummachines 808 and 909 - left such an imprint on electronic music like this monophone bassline synthie. Originally invented for musicians in need of a bassline player, the TB-303 was a real flop... Until some kids like [Phuture](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phuture) get hooked by the quirky sounds of the 303. And still the kids like to torture those knobs till some phunky acid bubbles its way through the speakers.

{% include mp3 %}

Already in 2009 Tribe Toolz released a first Acid Compilation full of tributes to the sound of the Roland TB-303. One year later they return with another 18 tracks celebrating [Acid](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acid_house) with all kind of flavors from chicago house over newskool acidlike bombs to classical acid house.

I agree.

_**Acid will never die!**_</content><author><name>Moritz »mo.« Sauer</name></author><category term="acid" /><category term="chicago house" /><category term="House" /><category term="Techno" /><category term="tribe toolz" /><summary type="html">Aciiiiid! // If we believe the peepz at Tribe Toolz today is the (un)official birthday of the fabulous Roland TB-303 synthesizer. No synthesizer - except the drummachines 808 and 909 - left such an imprint on electronic music like this monophone bassline synthie. Originally invented for musicians in need of a bassline player, the TB-303 was a real flop… Until some kids like Phuture get hooked by the quirky sounds of the 303. And still the kids like to torture those knobs till some phunky acid bubbles its way through the speakers. MP3 – Click to listen Mattias Fridell - &amp;quot;Die Kamera Läuft&amp;quot; (MP3) David Ramaszeder - &amp;quot;Pattern1&amp;quot; (MP3) Tobias Hoermann - &amp;quot;Acid 3-4&amp;quot; (MP3) Already in 2009 Tribe Toolz released a first Acid Compilation full of tributes to the sound of the Roland TB-303. One year later they return with another 18 tracks celebrating Acid with all kind of flavors from chicago house over newskool acidlike bombs to classical acid house. I agree. Acid will never die!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/cover_toolz303-II.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Grillo – »Fireworks Remixes« (Homework Records)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/1660-grillo-fireworks-remixes-homework-records" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grillo – »Fireworks Remixes« (Homework Records)" /><published>2010-12-27T18:18:17+01:00</published><updated>2010-12-27T18:18:17+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/grillo-fireworks-remixes-homework-records</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/hiphop/1660-grillo-fireworks-remixes-homework-records">***Italian HipHop Instrumentals*** // Homework Records represent Italys finest music if we speak about modern Hip Hop instrumentals. Like [Apes on Tapes]({{ site.url }}{{ site.baseurl }}/?s=Apes+on+Tapes) also Grillo is on the spearhead of modern beats. After his great debut called &quot;Fireworks&quot; the label refined his tracks with five excellent remixes.

&lt;!--mp3links--&gt;


  
[Grillo - &quot;Brown Box (Fulgeance Remix)&quot; (MP3)](http://mp3.phlow.de/phlow_2010/02._fulgeance_-_fireworks_remixes_-_brown_box_fulgeance_interstella_funk_remix_.mp3)
  
&lt;!--mp3linksend--&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;!--adsense--&gt;

The sound of Grillo is pure, very digital and funky. On &quot;Fireworks&quot; we listen to crispy beats, clicks, snares and solid kicks. Most of the tracks are build on some melodic grooves. This made me rewind the album to listen again to slow movers like &quot;Clicks&quot; or the fantastic hit &quot;Be aware&quot;.

Now we get the remixes and what can I say? I like the reworks even a little bit more. Each producer kept the digital sound of Grillo but managed to throw some of his delicate herbs and skills into the bowl. Just listen to the remix of &quot;Be Aware&quot; of Costa. Filled with some humour we nod to a straight-into-your-face pop hook. My favorite right now is the jazzy and funky retouch of Fulgeance on &quot;Brown Box&quot;. If this one won't make you smile and move, I don't know...

**Thumbs up, once again for the skills, beats and taste of Homework Records! Italys finest!**

## MP3 HipHop Music Download

**Download:** [Grillo - &quot;Fireworks Remixes&quot; (ZIP-Archive)](http://www.homeworkrecords.net/_dl_hwr/hwr016.zip)
  
**Netlabel:** [Homework Records](http://www.homeworkrecords.net/)</content><author><name>Brigitte</name></author><category term="Apes on Tapes" /><category term="grillo" /><category term="hip hop instrumentals" /><category term="homework records" /><category term="Instrumental" /><category term="instrumental hiphop" /><category term="modern beats" /><summary type="html">Italian HipHop Instrumentals // Homework Records represent Italys finest music if we speak about modern Hip Hop instrumentals. Like Apes on Tapes also Grillo is on the spearhead of modern beats. After his great debut called “Fireworks” the label refined his tracks with five excellent remixes. Grillo - “Brown Box (Fulgeance Remix)” (MP3)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/cover_fireworks_grillo_remixes.png%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Mentz – »Piani EP« (www.humanworkshop.com)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/jazz/1614-mentz-piani-ep-www-humanworkshop-com" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mentz – »Piani EP« (www.humanworkshop.com)" /><published>2010-12-27T16:59:51+01:00</published><updated>2010-12-27T16:59:51+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/jazz/mentz-piani-ep-www-humanworkshop-com</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/jazz/1614-mentz-piani-ep-www-humanworkshop-com">***Jazzy Smokin Loops*** // Turn on your delicate hifi soundsystem, free a cigar out of its cuban box, lean back in your rocking chair and lit up the tobacco. Mentz is here to trip with you on some wonky and crackling jazz loops collected from dusty records. Feel the phlow while old memories pass by drift on those wonderful sounds of melancholy.

&lt;!--mp3links--&gt;


  
[Mentz - &quot;Los&quot; (MP3)](http://mp3.phlow.de/phlow_2010/01._mentz_-_piani_ep_-_los.mp3)
  
[Mentz - &quot;Introduction II&quot; (MP3)](http://mp3.phlow.de/phlow_2010/02._mentz_-_piani_ep_-_introduction_ii.mp3)
  
[Mentz - &quot;Vast&quot; (MP3)](http://mp3.phlow.de/phlow_2010/03._mentz_-_piani_ep_-_vast.mp3)
  
[Mentz - &quot;Squares&quot; (MP3)](http://mp3.phlow.de/phlow_2010/04._mentz_-_piani_ep_-_squares.mp3)
  
&lt;!--mp3linksend--&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;!--adsense--&gt;

/images/urbanexplorersklein.jpg&quot;Since his first release called &quot;Re-Locate&quot;, I wait for more music by Mentz. He is the classic producer who diggs deep into his vinyl selection to combine whisphering samples of jazz with some carefull beats in slow motion. Mentz spent last summer performing live with musicians and did extensive collaborations with a violinist called Roosje Raab, a Clarinet player called Wouter Suren and Krisztián Ákos Muhari on the trumpet. The result is this wonderful little EP.

I hope it won't take years again till the next Mentz release :)

## Video Trailer



## MP3 Jazz Music Download

**Download:** [Mentz - &quot;Piani EP&quot; (ZIP-Archive)](http://www.humanworkshop.com/force_download.php?file=mp3/mentz_piani_ep.rar)
  
**Artist-Website:** [www.mentz.nl](http://www.mentz.nl)
  
**Release:** [Mentz - &quot;Piani EP&quot;](http://www.humanworkshop.com/index.php?modus=e_zine&amp;sub=articles&amp;item=162)
  
**Netlabel:** [www.humanworkshop.com](http://www.humanworkshop.com)</content><author><name>Brigitte</name></author><category term="humanworkshop" /><category term="Jazz" /><category term="mentz" /><summary type="html">Jazzy Smokin Loops // Turn on your delicate hifi soundsystem, free a cigar out of its cuban box, lean back in your rocking chair and lit up the tobacco. Mentz is here to trip with you on some wonky and crackling jazz loops collected from dusty records. Feel the phlow while old memories pass by drift on those wonderful sounds of melancholy. Mentz - “Los” (MP3) Mentz - “Introduction II” (MP3) Mentz - “Vast” (MP3) Mentz - “Squares” (MP3)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/cover_mentz_piani_ep.jpg%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Marko Fürstenberg – »Gesamtlaufzeit« (Thinner)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/techno/1484-marko-fuerstenberg-gesamtlaufzeit" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marko Fürstenberg – »Gesamtlaufzeit« (Thinner)" /><published>2010-12-27T16:01:13+01:00</published><updated>2010-12-27T16:01:13+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/techno/marko-fuerstenberg-gesamtlaufzeit</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mp3-music-download/techno/1484-marko-fuerstenberg-gesamtlaufzeit">&quot;Gesamtlaufzeit&quot; is a techno journey into icy landscapes and deep atmospheres full of echoes, sonic reflections and floating chords. Produced in 2003 Marko Fürstenberg also known as Surphase this album is not just only a selection of techno tracks. No, it's one of those rare albums, where we glide from one song into the other, experiencing different moods but always feel the flow. 

&lt;!--mp3links--&gt;


  
[Marko Fürstenberg - &quot;In Der Pappelei&quot; (MP3)](http://ftp.scene.org/pub/music/groups/thinner/%5bthn047%5d_08-marko_fuerstenberg_-_in_der_pappelei.mp3)
  
[Marko Fürstenberg - &quot;Mimerlaven&quot; (MP3)](http://ftp.scene.org/pub/music/groups/thinner/%5bthn047%5d_06-marko_fuerstenberg_-_mimerlaven.mp3)
  
[Marko Fürstenberg - &quot;Flüssige Reihe&quot; (MP3)](http://ftp.scene.org/pub/music/groups/thinner/%5bthn047%5d_05-marko_fuerstenberg_-_fluessige_reise.mp3)
  
&lt;!--mp3linksend--&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;!--adsense--&gt;

I hyped this DubTechno release many times, I am sorry for that. But this classy DubTechno album by Marko Fürstenberg has to be promoted also here on Phlow-Magazine.com because it is **still one the best DubTechno albums ever** and **one of the first netaudio longplayer** which grabbed my attention from beginning to end.

&quot;Gesamtlaufzeit&quot; is so amazing because you travel together with the artist from music gig to music gig. For his album Marko Fürstenberg composed smooth rockin DubTechno-tracks along with calm ambientish songs. Some of the songs where produced while travelling through Germany. If you imagine how the musician sits in the train, looks out the window and sees all the trees, houses, landscapes flying by, the sound fits perfect. Also it's a perfect statement how you get sucked into techno...

**A netaudio classic!**

## MP3 DubTechno Music Download

**Download:** [Marko Fürstenberg - &quot;Gesamtlaufzeit LP&quot; (ZIP-Archive)](http://ftp.scene.org/pub/music/groups/thinner/zip/%5bthn047%5d-marko_fuerstenberg_-_gesamtlaufzeit.zip)
  
**Artist-Website:** [Marko Fürstenberg](http://www.surphase.com/)
  
**Netlabel:** [Thinner](http://thinner.cc)</content><author><name>Moritz »mo.« Sauer</name></author><category term="classic" /><category term="DubTechno" /><category term="fürstenberg" /><category term="gesamtlaufzeit" /><category term="House" /><category term="netaudio" /><category term="Techno" /><category term="thinner" /><summary type="html">“Gesamtlaufzeit” is a techno journey into icy landscapes and deep atmospheres full of echoes, sonic reflections and floating chords. Produced in 2003 Marko Fürstenberg also known as Surphase this album is not just only a selection of techno tracks. No, it’s one of those rare albums, where we glide from one song into the other, experiencing different moods but always feel the flow. Marko Fürstenberg - “In Der Pappelei” (MP3) Marko Fürstenberg - “Mimerlaven” (MP3) Marko Fürstenberg - “Flüssige Reihe” (MP3)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22title%22=%3E%22/images/thn047_00-marko_f%C3%BCrstenberg_-_gesamtlaufzeit.jpg%22%7D" /></entry></feed>